早期的Android版本中并没有CursorLoader
Early versions of Android
don't have cursor loaders.
相反，当ContentProvider的数据发生改变时
Instead, the cursor adapter requeried
the database on the main UI thread,
CursorAdapter在UI主线程中请求数据库
when data from a content
provider changed.
它会造成很多应用程序的屏幕出现卡顿（显示帧率会下降）
This caused frame rate
drops in many applications.
所以第一个答案毫无疑问是肯定有弊端的。
The first answer is a definite yes.
我们关注了AsyncTasks之类的元素如何与UI线程进行绑定。
We noted how things like async
tasks are bound to the UI.
所以很小的一些变化，比如屏幕旋转，
So something as little
as an orientation change
会造成activity停止直到请求完成。
could cause the query to complete
after the activity stops.
因此另一个答案也是肯定的。
So that's another definite yes.
cursor与activity进行绑定也意味着
The cursor being tied to the activity
also means that the data would
当屏幕发生旋转时数据也要被重新读取，
generally have to be requeried
when the screen rotates, so
所以这样做肯定是有弊端的。
there are definitely disadvantages.